Associated Industries of New York State / The Business Council of New York State; Records apap043
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legal Counsel Records, Files, 1920; 1945-1947; 1952-1980; 9; 1 cubic foot
  - Pension Plan, 1958-1961 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 2)
  - Pension Plan, 1958-1959; 1966-1970; 1975 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 3)
  - Pension Plan, 1976-1979 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 4)
  - Pension Plan, Proposed, 1958-1959 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 5)
  - Pension Trust Agreement, 1952-1964 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 6)
  - Pregnancy Disability Benefits, 1977 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 7)
  - Schuler, Raymond T., Employment File, 1977-1979 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 8)
  - Social Security, 1976-1978 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 9)
  - Unemployment Insurance, 1971-1974; 1977 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 10)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 9 (9-Legal Counsel Records, Files), Folder 11-13)
- Auditor's Reports, 1918-1927; 10; 0.1 cubic ft.
  General auditor's reports, statements of assets, statements of receipts and disbursements.
  - Auditor's Reports, 1918-1927 (Box 9 (10-Auditor's Reports), Folder 14)
- Publications from other sources, 1957-1980; 11; 0.6 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically by title and chronologically thereafter.
  Newsletters on subjects of interest to AINY. Empire News (1957-76), news releases and bulletins from the Empire State Chamber of Commerce (1979), The Advisor and Research and Education (1958-60, 1968-69), Legislative Digest (1969), "Legislative Report" (1970).
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, Empire News, 1957-1976 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 15)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, News Releases and Bulletins, 1979 January-1979 March (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 16)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, News Releases and Bulletins, 1979 March-1979 May (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 17)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, News Releases and Bulletins, 1979 May-1979 August (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 18)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, News Releases and Bulletins, 1979 August-1979 October (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 19)
  - Empire State Chamber of Commerce, News Releases and Bulletins, 1979 October-1980 June (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 20)
  - Legislative Digest, 1969 March-1969 June (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 21)
  - Legislative Report, 1970 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 22)
  - Unemployment Benefit Advisors, Publications (contains The Advisor and Research and Education)., 1956-1957 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 23)
  - Unemployment Benefit Advisors, Publications, 1958 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 24)
  - Unemployment Benefit Advisors, Publications, 1959-1960 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 25)
  - Unemployment Benefit Advisors, Publications, 1968-1969 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Digest, 1969 March-1969 June (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Report, publication of New York Bar Association, 1970 (Box 9 (11-Publications from other sources), Folder 28)
- Website of the Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1996 December 19 - 2017 March 27; 12; 364 captures
  URL
  www.bcnys.org
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: NYS Business Council
  created_date: 2016-02-09T14:14:23Z
  created_by: gwiedeman
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:55Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1996 December 19
    This crawl was performed by the Internet Archive, not the UAlbany web archiving program, so the provenance is unknown.
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1997 January 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1997 January 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1997 April 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1997 October 18
    Meta tag for keywords: New York State, Albany, business, government, capital, capitol, association, constitutional convention, membership, member, legislature, benefits, discounts, seminars, conferences, public policy, environment, health, transportation, government affairs, small business, energy, telecommunications, workers' compensation, consumer products, insurance, financial services, construction, taxation, osha, labor, human resources, unemployment compensation
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1997 December 24
    Meta tag for keywords: New York State, Albany, business, government, capital, capitol, association, liability, membership, member, legislature, benefits, discounts, seminars, conferences, public policy, environment, health, transportation, government affairs, small business, energy, telecommunications, workers' compensation, consumer products, insurance, financial services, construction, taxation, osha, labor, human resources, unemployment compensation
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 January 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 February 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 April 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 December 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 December 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1998 December 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 February 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 February 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 February 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 April 17
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 April 28
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 1999 May 2
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 February 29
    Meta tag for keywords: New York State, Albany, business, government, capital, capitol, association, liability, membership, legislature, benefits, tort reform, seminars, conferences, public policy, environment, health, transportation, government affairs, small business, energy, telecommunications, workers' compensation, consumer products, insurance, financial services, construction, taxation, osha, labor, human resources, unemployment compensation
    Meta tag for description: The Business Council of New York State is a statewide association of over 4,000 member businesses, working to create an economic renaissance for New York State and its people.
    Meta tag for author: Gillian McLaughlin, mclaughl@nysnet.net
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 March 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 March 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 May 10
    Meta tag for author: Linda Costello, costello@nysnet.net
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 May 19
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 June 13
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 June 21
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 August 15
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 December 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2000 December 15
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 February 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 February 4
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 February 24
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 March 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 March 1
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 March 9
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 March 31
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 April 4
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 July 21
  - The Business Council of New York State Home Page, 2001 September 23
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2001 November 30
    Meta tag for author: Linda Costello, linda.costello@bcnys.org
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 March 27
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 March 31
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 May 24
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 June 3
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 July 20
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 August 2
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 September 19
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 September 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 September 24
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 September 25
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 October 7
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 October 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 October 31
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 November 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 November 27
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2002 November 29
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 January 22
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 February 12
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 February 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 March 30
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 April 10
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 April 24
  - 502 Bad Gateway, 2003 May 28
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 May 30
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 June 10
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 June 18
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 June 22
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 August 1
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 August 6
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 September 19
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 September 28
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 October 14
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 October 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 October 26
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 November 18
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 December 2
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 December 14
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2003 December 23
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 January 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 March 22
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 April 6
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 May 20
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 4
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 10
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 11
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 12
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 23
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 26
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 June 29
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 July 1
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 July 7
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 July 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 July 24
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 14
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 17
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 25
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 26
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 August 31
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 September 2
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 September 3
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 September 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 September 25
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 October 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 October 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 November 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 November 19
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 November 21
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 November 28
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 December 5
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 December 11
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 December 14
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2004 December 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 2
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 6
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 7
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 14
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 15
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 26
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 January 27
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 February 3
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 February 3
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 February 11
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 February 19
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 March 3
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 March 4
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 March 16
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 March 17
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 March 26
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 April 1
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 April 8
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 April 20
  - Home Page - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 April 26
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 May 16
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 May 20
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 May 30
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 1
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 2
  - New Domain, 2005 June 3
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 8
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 9
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 17
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 18
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 23
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 25
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 27
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 June 30
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 July 11
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 July 23
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 8
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 11
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 14
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 24
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 27
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 August 30
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 September 15
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 September 21
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 October 24
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 October 25
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 October 30
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 November 4
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 November 5
  - Home to The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 November 9
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 November 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 November 30
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 7
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2005 December 29
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 January 3
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 January 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 January 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 January 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 February 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 February 1
  - Under Construction, 2006 February 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 February 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 February 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 February 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 10
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 March 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 April 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 April 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 April 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 April 26
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 May 11
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 May 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 June 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 June 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 June 15
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 July 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 July 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 July 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 July 18
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 August 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 August 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 August 20
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 August 29
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 September 10
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 September 30
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 October 8
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 10
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 17
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 November 23
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 1
  - Under Construction, 2006 December 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 7
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2006 December 28
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 11
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 16
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 21
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 January 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 February 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 February 3
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 February 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 March 4
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 April 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 April 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 May 7
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 June 6
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 June 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 July 7
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 July 14
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 August 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 August 31
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 September 13
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 September 24
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 September 25
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 September 27
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 September 29
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 1
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 2
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 4
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 5
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 12
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2007 October 26
  - The Business Council of New York State, Inc., 2008 April 13